Good morning America, nationwide protests.
Thousands of no-kings rallies held across the country.
When protesters are under attack, what do we do?
Stand up, fight back.
Voicing opposition to Trump administration policies.
Organizers saying millions of Americans taking part.
GMA covering it all coast to coast.
Possible ceasefire violation.
The State Department reporting that Hamas is
planning an imminent attack on Palestinians in Gaza,
which would violate its peace deal with Israel.
The response from Hamas this morning.
Shut down anxiety.
Furloughed federal workers with no paychecks facing tough decisions.
Where can I find a zero interest loan
or am I going to have to get a side gig?
As 42 million Americans stand to lose
food stamp benefits in just weeks,
with Republicans and Democrats deadlocked in Washington.
Heading to trial,
former sheriff's deputy Sean Grayson
charged with murdering Sonia Massey,
who called 911 for help.
The jury to decide whether it was self-defense.
Breaking news,
the brazen heist at the world famous Louvre Museum in Paris.
Thieves using chainsaws to open display
cases stealing priceless objects.
The museum shut down.
GMA health alerts the shocking loss of R&B legend
D'Angelo putting a tight focus on the health
of black men and one of the deadliest cancers.
The symptoms you shouldn't ignore and
the importance of regular checkups.
And college football stunners.
George's come from behind win over Mississippi
led by Gunnar Stockton's four TD passes.
And Frasier walks in.
And Bandy scores their biggest win in decades.
All the highlights ahead.
Plus ESPN's Herm Edwards looks forward
to this weekend's top NFL games.
Live from ABC News headquarters in New York City.
It's Sunday.
Good morning America.
Gio has been talking so much trash
because your NFL picks are destroying us.
It ain't trash.
Truly knocking it out of the park.
Man. All right,
we're gonna get to all of that later on.
We have a lot to cover this morning,
including some breaking news out of Paris.
France's culture minister reporting a robbery at the
famed Louvre Museum home to Leonardo da Vinci's Mona Lisa.
New images coming in this morning of a ladder at the back
of the museum in Paris as police responded to the heist.
Yes, all over the world.
People will be talking about that story today.
Also ahead,
the disturbing new details in the search for Cata
Scott,
the Philadelphia woman who disappeared just over two weeks ago.
Human remains discovered
behind an abandoned school.
We have the latest coming up.
Oh, that's just so awful.
But first
we do begin here with the nationwide no Kings
protests targeting the Trump administration.
Organizers say seven million people took part
in thousands of events across the country.
ABC's Andrew Dimbert was on the streets here
in New York and he's here with a round up.
Good morning, Andrew.
Good morning,
Gio. It was the second round of no Kings protests.
Large crowds demonstrating in cities coast to
coast in response to what they call an abuse
of power by President Trump and his administration.
Hey,
hey, ho ho.
Donald Trump has got to go.
Nearly seven million people in over 2,700 cities
nationwide taking to the streets Saturday,
according to organizers protesting what they
say is the abuse of power by President Donald
Trump, calling it no Kings Day.
When protesters are under attack, what do we do?
Rally is held in all 50 states,
a majority of them peaceful from Florida,
Arizona and Texas.
We will never accept his totalitarianism
to the major cities of San Diego,
Atlanta and Chicago.
In the heart of New York City,
we protect our people.
Hordes of demonstrators flooding Manhattan's busiest streets.
It's time to start upholding the Constitution.
Democracy is dying and we have to save it.
There's no place for Kings in America.
Donald Trump is attempting to bully us and intimidate us to
the point that we are unwilling to stand up across the coast.
Aggressive ICE raids are just one of many of Trump's policies,
motivating protesters to show up in Los Angeles.
Our Alex Stone was on the ground here in
the Los Feliz neighborhood of Los Angeles.
Several thousand people have come out,
some with their children,
others walking their dogs.
They say that they want to be peaceful,
but they want their voices heard.
Meanwhile, at the nation's capital.
We, the people.
More than 200,000 people gathering
amid the government shutdown.
Our Christian Cordero was there.
In Washington,
D.C.,
a city filled with federal workers
who are currently furloughed,
tens of thousands of people
have shown up here at a pivotal moment,
fighting back against what they call an assault on democracy.
To now be stuck, not getting paid,
worrying about how my family is gonna get it
through this period
has been very stressful.
This is the second wave of protests organized by No Kings,
a network of progressive organizations
fighting against the Trump agenda,
drawing in two million more participants since the
first nationwide demonstration in June.
The message even being spread internationally
with demonstrations in Mexico,
Canada,
and
Spain.
There were no immediate reports of violence or arrests,
according to several local police
departments earlier in the week when asked about the rallies,
President Trump telling Fox News,
quote, I am not a king.
Okay, Andrew Denver, thank you for that.
We appreciate it is now day 19 of the government shutdown and
for federal workers and others waiting on their paychecks.
The economic impact is intensifying.
ABC's senior White House correspondent Selena
Wang is in Washington with what comes next here.
Selena, good morning.
Yeah,
good morning with day 19 and there is still no end in sight.
The longer this drives on for the more painful it is for millions of
Americans and the bigger the impact on our economy.
This morning, growing anxiety
across America as the government
shutdown stretches into its fourth week,
officials warning 42 million Americans
could lose their food stamp benefits in
two weeks with snap on track to run out of funding.
Food banks across the
country preparing for a surge in demand.
The president ramping up pressure on
Democrats already freezing billions of
dollars in infrastructure projects and
blue states and threatening to slash programs.
We're cutting Democrat programs
that we didn't want,
you know,
giveaways,
welfare programs,
etcetera,
and we're
doing that and we're cutting them permanently.
More than 750,000 federal
workers for load, more than 4000 fired.
But the White House says some,
including military troops,
FBI agents and DHS officers will get paid.
We got
the people that we want paid, paid.
Okay, and we want the FBI paid.
We want
the military paid.
But thousands of other federal workers
like air traffic controller Mike Christine,
who's also a union representative,
are going without pay.
You're talking about it while you're at work with your
co workers and just figuring out where can I find a zero
interest loan or am I going to have to get a side gig?
At what point does this actually impact safety in the skies?
Every day it goes on.
You know, a distraction turns into a hazard.
You throw the headset on,
you're supposed to forget everything that happened at home.
But when you're
starting to think about I can't even pay the mortgage,
like what are we going to tell?
It's it's it's very, very frustrating.
But on Capitol Hill,
a stalemate Democrats holding
firm on their demand to extend expiring Obamacare subsidies.
Part of the problem is that
House Republicans are nowhere to be found.
Literally
have been on vacation for three
consecutive weeks.
So you heard what the House minority
leader said there and the House is
again out all next week as talks in the Senate are at a standstill.
So Republicans are saying they will not negotiate
on health care when the government is shut
down.
But what that means is that thousands of
federal workers are wondering when they'll
get their next paycheck.
Yet members of Congress,
guys,
are still getting paid.
Janay, they certainly are still getting paid.
Selena Wang, thank you so much.
Now let's bring in Chief Washington correspondent Jonathan Karl,
who'll be hosting this week
later this morning to talk about all of this.
John, thanks for being with us.
Talk to us about the this government shutdown.
Is there any ending in sight as we are leading up to day 20?
I mean,
honestly,
Janay,
no,
I don't see any sign of even serious negotiations going underway.
The Republicans seem to have calculated that the Democrats are
feeling the pain from this and that they'll pay the political price
because they voted against the temporary funding bill.
The Democrats are getting a lot of positive reinforcement from
rank and file Democrats across the country who are looking
for the party leaders to show a fight against Donald Trump.
So I don't see any real signs of this.
And here's the thing.
And I'll be talking to,
of course,
the speaker of the House exclusively
this morning and also Hakeem Jeffries,
the Democratic leader.
The House is not in session.
The House is closed for business.
There are no hearings.
There are no votes.
Nothing is happening in the House.
So I'll talk to both of them about that.
There's not even,
you know,
talk about no movement at all.
They're literally not in session.
That's what's so striking because they are still getting paid as
other federal workers have to go to work and are not getting paid.
John, let's also turn to the war in Ukraine.
President Zelensky,
he walked away from his meeting with President Trump empty handed.
Trump calling for both sides to lay down arms immediately.
Talk to us about the fallout.
So we saw part of this on you know play out
play out in.
in front of the television cameras as they sat
down for lunch.
Zalensky Trump and their various teams.
You know it was a pretty
well meaning affair compared to what happened in
February when you had that blow up in the Oval Office.
But I'm told that
the second meeting which was without television cameras
that took place in the Oval Office really was quite tense.
Not quite what we saw in February.
But
Zalensky came here with one major goal and that is to
get more advanced weapons from the United States
including those Tomahawk missiles so he could bring the
fight to the Russians on Russian territory to try to you
know to try to have some more progress against the Russians.
And he came away
with absolutely nothing.
Of course President Trump says he's going
to meet with Vladimir Putin in Hungary.
He said perhaps sometime
in two weeks we'll see how that goes.
But I Zalensky is not going to be at that meeting.
So once again Zalensky seems to be facing
this without significant American support and not getting
the support that he really said he needed and thought he
had a good chance of getting in this meeting with Trump.
Yeah.
As the fighting continues.
John Karl we appreciate you being with us
and make sure to tune into this week later.
John as he mentioned has exclusive interviews with
House Speaker Mike Johnson and minority leader
Hakeem Jeffries.
All right.
A big show ahead.
And now to the Mideast and the U.S.
State Department with a warning that Hamas
could be planning an attack on Palestinian
civilians.
That's a potential violation of the ceasefire.
And ABC's Marcus Moore joins us now from London with this.
Good morning Marcus.
Good morning.
A lot is happening this morning.
Both sides are now accusing the other of violating the ceasefire.
This morning Israel has conducted new airstrikes in Gaza
and according to Israel this follows multiple attacks that
Hamas launched against IDF soldiers beyond the yellow line.
Now all of this comes after that State Department warning.
Now Hamas says is targeting criminal gains and has called
the warning Israeli propaganda and a false pretension.
And then you have incidents along the yellow
line where IDF troops have partially withdrawn.
Yesterday the IDF killed a family of 11 Palestinians
who they said approached that line and Prime
line where IDF troops have partially withdrawn.
Yesterday the IDF killed a family of 11 Palestinians
who they said approached that line and Prime Minister
Netanyahu has also said that the Rafah crossing along Gaza's
southern border with Egypt will remain closed until the
remaining bodies of dead hostages are returned to Israel.
With no one was under any illusions about how
difficult this ceasefire would be to maintain.
And we are seeing that this morning.
Yeah.
All of just highlighting how fragile the situation still remains.
Marcus Moore for us.
Thank you.
We turn now to two survivors of a military strike on a suspected drug
smuggling submersible vessel now returning to their home countries.
President Trump says four people he describes as narco
terrorists were on board the vessel when military forces
carried out the strike in the Caribbean on Thursday.
Trump yesterday revealing that two of the survivors are being
sent back to Ecuador and Colombia for detention and prosecution.
One of them reportedly arrived in Ecuador
yesterday and remains under medical observation.
All right.
Now to what appears to be devastating news in the
case of missing Philadelphia woman last seen two
weeks ago while working at a nursing home ABC.
It's Morgan Norwood has more now on the search for Kata Scott.
Morgan you brought us the story
yesterday and now we have this update.
The update that we want to be bringing you this morning.
A heartbreaking development in the search for 23 year old Kata Scott.
After more than two weeks of searching police say a very
specific anonymous tip led detectives back to this abandoned
elementary school where they uncovered a shallow grave in the
woods with remains that they believe to be those of Kata Scott.
Now the medical examiner of course is working to confirm the
identity and investigators are in touch with Scott's family.
Now keep in mind this is the same location where officers say
they found her debit card and phone case last week during that
search.
Meanwhile attention is back on 21 year old Keon King the man
already arrested in connection with Kata's disappearance.
You see him there.
Police say that he was previously charged in
another alleged kidnapping back in January.
But of course we know he walked free after posting cash bail.
Now authorities say that King was the last person seen with
her and they believe that she did not leave with him willingly.
The suspect is being held on a two and a half million dollar
bail expected in court for his preliminary hearing next month.
All eyes on this and whether he will
have additional charges of course authorities are investigating that.
And we remember her family
yesterday saying that they just wanted her
back home so this is just heartbreaking.
We're thinking
of them.
Morgan thank you so much.
Now to jury selection set to start in the murder trial of a
former sheriff's deputy accused of killing a woman
who called 911 for help and ABC's Olivia Rubin is
here now with this.
Good morning Olivia.
Geo good morning.
It has been over a year since Sonia Massey
was killed in her own home by a police officer
after calling 911 sparking international outrage.
Now that officer set to face a jury accused of murder.
This morning Sean Grayson the former deputy accused
of killing Sonia Massey is headed to trial this week.
Sheriff's office Grayson charged with first degree murder in a
case prosecutors say revolves around body camera footage showing
his response to Massey's home after she called police to report.
A disturbance last July it sounds like
somebody was banging on the side of my
house.
I don't know.
I'll get y'all come and see throughout the six minute
encounter Massey struggling to answer questions.
Her family saying she had
recently been experiencing mental illness.
What is your last name?
Should not think much last name things
quickly escalate after deputies told her
she could remove a pot of boiling water from the stove.
I'll rebuke you in the name of Jesus.
You better not.
I swear to God I'll shoot you right in your face.
Drop the f***ing pot.
Shots fired.
According to the autopsy report the
bullet entered under Massey's left eye.
Grayson never denied firing saying in
court documents he feared for his life.
He is pleading not guilty to murder
aggravated battery with a firearm and
misconduct.
In order for the jury to convict Grayson they would have to
believe that there was no reasonable
fear both objectively and subjectively
that Grayson was in fear of his life
whether it be death or serious injury.
Now
this trial has been moved to a different
location due to the extensive publicity
here and outside court this week activists and supporters planning to
rally with Massey's family.
All right Olivia Rubin for us we appreciate it.
College football now and some awesome games overnight.
ABC's Ike Kajachi is here with the highlights.
Hey Ike. Hey good morning Gia. What a Saturday it was in college
football the kind of day that shakes up the SEC in the playoff picture.
Let's start in Nashville.
Well Vanderbilt yes Vandy stunned the college football world.
The 17th ranked
Commodores up said number 10 LSU 31
to 24 and quarterback Diego Pavia was
electric throwing for one score running
for two more including a highlight real
Heisman style touchdown pose that fired up the whole crowd.
Vandy took down LSU
for the first time since 1990 their
biggest win in decades and over in
Athens a heavyweight shootout between
Georgia and Ole Miss more than lived up
to the hype.
The ninth ranked Bulldogs pulled away late beating number five Ole
Miss 43 to 35 after trailing in the second half.
Now Georgia's gonna Gunnar
Stockley gonna I should say.
He threw four touchdown passes three of them
tight end lost and lucky as the Bulldogs
defense finally clamped down in the
fourth quarter that preserved the
victory and then in Tuscaloosa rolled
tied Alabama making the statement the
sixth ranked Crimson Tide rolled past
number 11 Tennessee 37 to 20. The turning point
came just before halftime a stunning 99 yard pick
sick by Xavier Brown flipped the game entirely.
Quarterback Ty Simpson.
He threw for over 250 yards and two touchdowns as Bama stayed
unbeaten in the SEC and extended his mastery over the balls guys.
All right.
So you've got that covered Ike but let's switch gears.
It's hard to believe the NBA season starts this week.
Can you believe it.
The preseason is already in the books and the
regular season tips off Tuesday with a double header.
The reigning champion Oklahoma
City Thunder behind MVP Shea Gill just Alexander.
They start their title defense why Nicole
Yocos and the Nuggets look to reclaim the West.
And of course all eyes are on LeBron James entering
his 23rd and possibly final season at age 41. The NBA
he's still looking to make a final playoff push with
the Los Angeles Lakers even as he battles Sky Attica.
But don't count him out.
He's coming off at 20 points per game season.
Another all star nod.
Obviously the big news the big storylines are
everywhere from rookie sensation Cooper flag in Dallas.
Obviously Victor
Wemba Yama leading a resurgent Spurs team.
Yeah.
It's shaping up to be one of the most
star packed seasons ever guys.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Looking forward to all of it.
Some other big
news you have to Ike Jocchi.
All of favor.
Yeah.
Congratulations.
Honored yourself.
Tell
us about this honor.
Wow. Wow. Thank you.
First of all this is a surprise.
I didn't
know.
I'm going very sweating.
I don't know.
You know I got my master's degree over at
Quinnipiac University back in 2015 and
it was just such a great experience.
You know what I mean.
Like the warmth of the hug I felt as soon as I walked in there.
And it really just jump started everything.
You know I mean got me to my first
station came back started teaching the
started teaching there as an adjunct professor
and it's just really been an honor
to just have that link to Quinnipiac.
Well, congratulations, hall of favor.
You know, of course we love having you here
as part of our family.
Did you see they even showed a video?
I know.
He picked up.
Let's go.
All right, I will check back with you in a bit.
In our next hour here on GMA,
we're also gonna talk about the NFL.
We've got that covered.
ESPN's Coach Herm Edwards
previews the big games, including the Giants,
hoping to keep a winning streak going.
Also,
you don't want to miss Gio's winning streak.
Yeah, there's that.
Yes.
Also coming up here on GMA,
crucial medical information for all men,
especially black men in the wake of the death of R&B legend D'Angelo.
Very important story.
And that late word out of Paris,
the world famous Louvre Museum shut down
for the day following a shocking heist.
You're watching GMA on this Sunday morning.
Stay with us.
All right,
and we are gonna start this half hour
here with the breaking news from Paris.
Thieves staging a heist at the Louvre
Museum targeting priceless jewelry displays,
and
ABC's Marcus Moore has more on that.
Good morning again, Marcus.
Hey, Gio, good morning.
These details are still coming in,
but here's what we know right
now.
This was a bold and sophisticated robbery.
It happened at the Louvre this morning as it
was opening.
The robbery reported around 930. Authorities
say three to four robbers arrived
at the museum in Paris,
used a ladder at one point and a freight elevator to reach the Apollo
Room.
Their authorities say they broke windows
and used small chainsaws to steal jewelry,
the crown jewels.
The robbery itself lasted about seven
minutes and nine pieces of invaluable
jewelry were taken.
Those robbers took off on motorbikes.
Now, one American witness who
was there when this happened described the chaos.
She says she saw the police running
into the museum,
which was eventually evacuated,
and it still shut down.
On a Sunday like this,
the museum sees tens of thousands of visitors,
so for them to close it is truly extraordinary.
Now,
there were no injuries reported,
and now there's an urgent manhunt for the suspects.
The Interior Minister said their team
of robbers seemed highly trained.
Whit.
All right, Marcus, more for us.
Thank you.
All right.
Now we are going to turn to the spotlight
on black men's health and life expectancy.
Six days ago,
we learned of the death of R and B legend D'Angelo at the age of 51,
his
family revealing he was privately dealing with pancreatic cancer.
Joining us now to
unpack more of this conversation is ABC News
medical correspondent Dr. Darian Sutton.
So
many people were shocked to hear about this,
shocked at his age,
and we've seen this trend
of younger men dying from these cancers.
D'Angelo after a battle with one of the deadliest pancreatic
cancers.
So Dr. Sutton,
what are some of those common red flag
symptoms that folks should look out for?
It's a critical reminder about black men's health overall.
Now,
pancreatic cancer is notoriously silent,
which makes it a challenge mainly because
there's no screening method for it.
So early recognition of these symptoms is really key.
And the symptoms that you want to pay attention
to are things like unexplained weight loss,
fatigue, jaundice or dark urine.
This is because there's a component of our blood called
bilirubin that can rise as a result of the pancreatic cancer.
Again, there is no formal screening.
So talking to
your provider about your symptoms is essential.
You know,
and another reminder,
we've talked about this before.
According to the CDC, black men are among,
have them among the lowest life expectancy when we're talking
about all demographics of race and gender.
So what's behind this?
It's pretty significant.
And I want to put some of these numbers into perspective.
Black men,
Alaska native men,
American Indian men
have life expectancies of the shortest comparative
to overall numbers.
So seven to 10 years lower than the average of 73 years old.
Now, as far as the reasons behind this,
it is nuanced and complex.
Of course,
there's a genetic component to pay attention to,
but really what these numbers reflect
is a deep systemic inequity that exists within communities
that is played out within these numbers,
barriers to access to care,
unequal access to care.
A lot of that plays out into the examining room.
What's important to know is that these numbers
are not inevitable.
Making steps by seeing a primary care doctor
and getting screen can close that gap and make a difference.
Yeah, those are such troubling numbers.
And when you look at all men,
I mean,
so many wait till
it's too late to even go for their,
they don't go to the routine checkups.
So what's the message?
How do you help them prioritize all of that?
Approximately 50% of men in total
don't go to routine checkups.
It's so important to share that and to make sure
that we all understand the power of prevention.
I'm an emergency physician,
but my life's goal is keeping people out of the hospital.
And the way we do that is by screening effectively.
And I think many black men do not know
that they're at a higher risk.
Number one, for all of us,
everyone should be paying attention
to those three key numbers at the top,
cholesterol, sugar, blood pressure.
That's the key indicators of cardiovascular disease,
which is the leading cause of death.
But as far as other cancers that systemically and increased,
or we have an increased risk of is black men,
you want to pay attention to things like prostate cancer
and colon cancer.
These conversations should start in your early 40s
if you're high risk.
That doesn't just include black men.
For example, if you have a genetic risk,
if you have a family history of the BRCA gene,
we've talked about this before,
that increases your risk as well.
Again, these early conversations can save a life
because many people are just simply not aware
that they might have availability for increased screening
and earlier screening.
Truly important information.
As you point out,
these numbers don't have to be that way.
They don't have to be a number.
People can make a difference.
Absolutely.
Yeah, thank you.
Appreciate it, Dr. Sutton.
Okay, ESPN's Herm Edwards.
He's back with his take on all the big NFL games to watch
and sharing some predictions,
some predictions I'm especially skilled at.
Yo, yo.
Oh boy.
We'll be right back.
And welcome back to GMA,
week seven in the NFL season.
As we look ahead to the biggest games
and joining us now with his insights
this morning is ESPN football analyst,
our friend,
Herm Edwards.
Herm, it is good to see you, my friend.
Hey, coach.
Good to be with y'all.
We got some problems in the NFL right now,
but we're going to fix them.
Yeah, we got some problems.
Your Eagles,
your beloved Eagles,
you told us last week you didn't like how they were playing.
And now we saw what happened in their last game.
They lost to the Giants.
They're facing the Vikings.
What do you think?
Well,
I think this,
there's a running back in Philadelphia.
His name is Saquon Barkley.
He wears number 26 if you don't know who he is.
They need to figure out how to get him the ball again.
Think about it this way.
In the last two weeks,
he's touched the ball 18 times.
That's not good at all.
Running backs got an average of at least 25 touches a game.
You got to give this guy the ball to generate some
offense and then hopefully the offense can play good
enough and long enough to keep the defense off the field
because the defense is leaky right now.
So this will be a very interesting game
against the Viking team that is headed in the right direction.
See, and a lot of the video we're showing there,
it's the Eagles losing to the Giants.
The Giants,
they're now facing the Broncos this afternoon.
Can they make it two wins in a row, coach?
They can,
but this Bronco defense is really,
really good.
Think about it this way.
They only give up 16 points a game.
Hard to score against this Bronco defense.
You know what they do really well?
They sack the quarterback.
30 sacks already.
Lead the league and they take the ball away.
So if you're the Giants and you have this young quarterback,
you have to be careful with the ball.
It's going to be a field position game.
It might look ugly at times,
but make it an ugly game.
If you get behind against these Denver Broncos,
you're in trouble.
They do that to the quarterback.
Okay.
I didn't want to bring this up,
but I'm going to,
because last week I trusted you.
I picked the commanders to beat the Bears.
You know, I was with you all the way, Herm.
That did not go well as we know.
This week they're facing the Cowboys.
Both teams lost last week.
Who will rebound today?
What do you think?
Well,
Washington needs a rebound because
Washington is still in this division race,
along with Dallas,
to be quite honest.
Dallas has the number one offense in the National Football League,
but Jane Daniels is the key to this.
The Cowboys
have trouble stopping the run.
Well, guess what?
Jane Daniels in this Washington team,
they're second in the National Football
League running the football.
Now you see him throwing some passes to McCaffrey
and Ernst.
That's, that's part of the deal.
But his ability to run,
I think really poses a problem to the Dallas Cowboys.
Herm,
I've got 99 problems,
but who's with Herm ain't one.
Let's go ahead
and roll the numbers.
Let's see that chart.
Let's look at the scores.
Yeah,
there we go.
So I've got four.
I'm still in the lead.
Janay's got three though.
She's got, you know what you forget?
There's 10 games left.
There's long seasons.
Exactly.
That's what I'm talking about.
Go ahead.
Just looking at the data.
You've got two, Witt's got one.
So now on Monday Night Football,
we've got the Bucs facing the
Lions.
What do you think?
Where's the game at?
That's what I was thinking too.
Wait, where's the game at?
Where's the game at?
Is it at the Buccaneers?
I don't remember.
Sorry.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't?
The Detroit Lions.
Okay.
I'm taking the Lions.
All right.
All right, what do you think?
Can someone in the control room tell?
I'm going, oh, it's in Detroit.
We just, we're just told it's in Detroit.
Oh, it's in Detroit.
Oh,
I'm definitely going with the Lions running game.
Jamar Gibbs,
Jamira Gibbs, he's on my fantasy team.
Going with him.
Going with the Lions.
I'm gonna go with the Lions too.
Yeah.
So I was thinking about that.
And my Florida people are going to
have a tough time in Detroit's weather.
So I'm going to say the Lions too.
All right.
Yeah.
No, no, no, no.
Don't, no, no, don't join us.
Yeah.
Don't go out on the limit and take your Buccaneers.
Don't join us.
You get all the answers and all of a sudden,
yeah,
I'm going to take the Lions too.
Yeah, right.
Exactly.
You tell them how it's done, Coach.
I'm with her.
You play to win the game.
There you go.
Don't forget the hello.
That's the most important thing, the jingle.
Hello.
It is hard to bet against Gio right now,
but we have a Monday night football doubleheader
tomorrow night starting with the Bucs versus the Lions
at seven Eastern on ABC,
then the Texans versus the Seahawks at 10 Eastern on ESPN.
Look at that board up there.
I'm so glad we keep it up.
Back now with our group chat
and the stories that piqued our interest this week.
So I will start.
And on Friday, I moderated a panel
as part of the March of Dimes,
it starts with Mom campaign.
The event was called The Collective and
it brought together influential CEOs,
changemakers
and advocates for conversations about maternal and infant health.
The panel I hosted there
included four women who shared powerful stories
about loss and resilience on their journeys
to motherhood and the impact that the
March of Dimes makes through research,
programming
and advocacy for moms and babies.
It's a reminder of the stark reality facing American families
and the staggering statistics on maternal
and infant mortality in this country,
which
we just continue to see high,
high rates that are really unacceptable and impact so many
families.
We were just talking to Darian Sutton,
the impact on black moms and babies higher
than their counterparts.
So a really just impactful event,
a reminder of the work to
be done.
I'm so glad you did that.
That was so important.
Very passionate about it, getting
the word out, raising awareness as well.
So thank you for that.
All right.
Mine's a little
bit different here.
Thursday Night Football,
we saw what was dubbed the Icy Hot Bowl.
I love the name of this 40 year old Joe Flacco and the Bengals
taking on 41 year old Aaron Rogers and the Pittsburgh Steelers.
So professional sports aside, it got me thinking
I should try out for the San Francisco 49. Yes,
yes.
Just kidding.
But seriously,
though,
across the country,
we're seeing this growing trend of older adults who are
playing sports and they're involved in athletics much longer.
Myself included everything from soccer, my
favorite sport to pickleball,
like the fastest growing sport in the country right now.
So I was thinking here,
if you want to be or are right now an aging athlete,
as they're called,
how do you properly train while avoiding injuries?
So I've had several injuries myself.
Yeah, you're dealing with the back.
I know, I know.
We reached out to Geo's buddy here,
celebrity fitness coach Don Saladino.
He's worked with some of the biggest names in
Hollywood from Ryan Reynolds to Hugh Jackman.
The list goes on.
So Don gave us these three simple tips here.
All right,
intensity buildup.
So if you're going to start a sport,
start slow,
what he calls dogging it.
About 50% intensity at first,
then build it up over time as your body adapts to the movements.
Training on all three.
And so important,
your workouts need to include full backwards,
side to side and rotational movements.
Yeah, so adding all of that in.
Here's the big one here,
the third one,
recovery,
added focus on rest and nutrition.
Take a listen to what he said about that.
My recovery is different than it was when I was 25. So I think understanding as someone in their 40s,
that they're going to have to put a lot more into recovery,
focusing on protein,
focusing on sleep
quality and understanding that you can't come
back day in and day out at 100% intensity,
learning to
adjust that I think are the three areas that need to be focused on.
By the way, dude's a beast.
Distracted by his biceps right there.
He's 48. 48. Talks about this,
but recovery,
that's been my issue.
I haven't given myself enough time for recovery.
Very, very important.
Big thanks to Don for those tips.
And he gives tips like that on Instagram at Don Saladino.
All right,
so I was walking through the park yesterday
and I realized, like it hit me,
the days are really getting shorter.
But I just want to show you these times here,
okay?
So this is what's happening.
At its peak on July 1st, look at the time here.
Sunrise in New York was at 5.28 AM, sunset 8.31.
Yesterday,
7.10 AM for that sunrise,
6.10 PM for the sunset.
So we're losing almost four hours of daylight right now.
And so I happen to love it.
I like it getting a little dark.
But I'm told that like one of the suggestions
is to use a light box that provides 10,000 lux of light
for 30 minutes each morning.
So you get that vitamin D.
So you can get that a little bit,
but just get outside.
Try to get outside as much as you can,
get that natural light.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
So important.
You're always the fall guy.
You like the fall.
I love the fall.
Yeah, not me.
My birthday.
Agree to disagree on that.
WineSnob72, Florida will have no problems
in Detroit because they play in a dome.
That's right.
Follow us on Instagram.
We'll see you.